[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "dog",
        "back": "собака",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "blue",
        "back": "синий",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "kitty",
        "back": "кошка",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "mouse",
        "back": "мышка",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "house",
        "back": "дом",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "diary",
        "back": "дневник",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "leg",
        "back": "нога",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "eye",
        "back": "глаз",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "box-shadow",
        "back": "тень",
        "setName":"CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "color",
        "back": "цвет",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "border-radius",
        "back": "скругление краев",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "background-image",
        "back": "фоновая картинка",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "font-weight",
        "back": "толщина шрифта",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "front": "font-family",
        "back": "шрифт",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "front": "background-color",
        "back": "цвет фона",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "front": "border",
        "back": "рамка",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "front": "margin",
        "back": "внешние отступы",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "front": "padding",
        "back": "внутренние отступы",
        "setName": "CSS-свойства"
    }
]